<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HungryHero</string>
    <string name="app_welcome">Welcome to HungryHero!</string>
    <string name="app_welcome_restaurant_text">Congratulations on successfully registering your restaurant! We are excited that you have joined our community.!</string>
    <string name="app_add_info">Complete the information about your restaurant!</string>
    <string name="app_add_info_text">Filling out the details of your restaurant is important so that customers can easily find you and learn more about what you offer.</string>
    <string name="app_add_menu">Add a menu</string>
    <string name="app_add_menu_text">Adding a menu is crucial as it allows customers to explore your offerings and make informed dining choices, enhancing their overall experience.</string>
    <string name="app_add_photos">Add photos</string>
    <string name="app_add_photos_text">Uploading photos is essential as it gives customers a visual insight into your restaurant\'s ambiance and dishes, making your establishment more appealing and inviting.</string>
    <string name="app_ready">You\'re all set!</string>
    <string name="app_ready_text">Now you can proceed to manage your restaurant within the app.</string>
    <string name="app_next">Next</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>

    <string-array name="wishes">
        <item>May your day be as sweet as your favorite dessert!|default_background.jfif</item>
        <item>Today is a perfect day for a cup of freshly brewed coffee.|default_background.jfif</item>
        <item>There\'s nothing better than a slice of warm bread with butter. Enjoy!|default_background.jfif</item>
        <item>Today seems like a great day for some delicious pasta. Bon appétit!|default_background.jfif</item>
        <item>Why not treat yourself to a delightful pastry today?|default_background.jfif</item>
        <item>A fresh salad might just be the refreshing meal you need today.|default_background.jfif</item>
        <item>May every bite you take today bring you joy and satisfaction!|default_background.jfif</item>
        <item>How about some fresh sushi today? It\'s always a good choice!|default_background.jfif</item>
        <item>Today is a perfect day for a slice of pizza. Enjoy!|default_background.jfif</item>
        <item>A homemade burger might just be the treat you need today.|default_background.jfif</item>
        <item>Why not indulge in some creamy ice cream today?|default_background.jfif</item>
        <item>A fresh juice can be the perfect start to your day.|default_background.jfif</item>
        <item>Today seems like a great day for a hearty sandwich.|default_background.jfif</item>
        <item>How about a refreshing smoothie to kickstart your day?|default_background.jfif</item>
        <item>A piece of chocolate cake is always a good idea. Enjoy!|default_background.jfif</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>